The Dvi Bhagavatap Purana calls the
divine mother as
Mahavidya, the supreme
knowledge. She is the mother of the
universe existing even before the
beginning of time. She appears to her
devotees in 10 forms called the Das
Mahawidyas. These are her tantric forms.
Each symbolizing an aspect of her
energy. Their worship was once performed
in secret in jungles, cremation grounds,
and the wilderness of mother
nature. A lack of proper spiritual
guidance and physical harm were real
possibilities for the seeker as they
navigated their external and internal
worlds. But not
anymore. Step into the digital realm of
the dash mahabidyas.
Unlock awakened
mantras, access sacred fire offerings
and invoke each mahavya with a dedicated
spiritual practice.
[Music]
reveal the wisdom, devotion and supreme
spiritual consciousness that has always
existed in you. For every Mahavya you
awaken, you will be granted a boon. Walk
the path of Mahavya
Tantra. Its
esoteric practices will undo the chains
that bind your mind and fill you with
untold devotion and bliss.
Peace, wealth, happiness and freedom can
be
yours. All you need is
[Music]
sincerity. Break free and awaken the
divine goddess in all her glory.